{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Gas Line Install \u0026 Repair Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40356/":{"taskOID":40356,"originalTaskOID":40356,"setID":650,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4161,"questionDisplayText":"Scope of Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the scope of the work? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair leak in gas line","answerDisplayText":"Repair leak in gas line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old gas lines","answerDisplayText":"Replace old gas lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Appliance gas hook-up","answerDisplayText":"Appliance gas hook-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6199,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4162,"questionDisplayText":"Appliances in Need of Gas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which appliance(s) need gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":942,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barbecue","answerDisplayText":"Barbecue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1313,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Central heating system","answerDisplayText":"Central heating system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4161,"questionDisplayText":"Scope of Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the scope of the work? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair leak in gas line","answerDisplayText":"Repair leak in gas line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old gas lines","answerDisplayText":"Replace old gas lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Appliance gas hook-up","answerDisplayText":"Appliance gas hook-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6199,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5216,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair leak in gas line","answerDisplayText":"Repair leak in gas line","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5273,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace old gas lines","answerDisplayText":"Replace old gas lines","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":808,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Appliance gas hook-up","answerDisplayText":"Appliance gas hook-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6199,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply gas line to appliance(s) in or near the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","answerDisplayText":"Supply new gas piping from the street to the home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4162,"questionDisplayText":"Appliances in Need of Gas","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which appliance(s) need gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":942,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barbecue","answerDisplayText":"Barbecue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1313,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Central heating system","answerDisplayText":"Central heating system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":942,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Barbecue","answerDisplayText":"Barbecue","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6135,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Stove/oven/cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1313,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Central heating system","answerDisplayText":"Central heating system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6863,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water heater","answerDisplayText":"Water heater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2796,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Generator","answerDisplayText":"Generator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40356/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40356,"taskName":"Gas Piping","taskDescription":"Repair or Install Gas Piping","xmTaskDescriptor":"Gas Line Install \u0026 Repair Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1103,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Gas Piping pipeline","textMessagingName":"Gas Piping","rolloverLongDesc":"In many jurisdictions, plumbers go through a separate training, certification \u0026/or licensing process to be permitted to work with gas.","rolloverShortDesc":"Plumber certified for gas work.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Install Gas Piping.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Gas Line \u0026 Gas Pipe Installation \u0026 Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Gas Piping","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gas Piping","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Gas Piping Project","urlName":"Gas-Piping","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Gas Line Installers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Gas Pipe Repair","searchKeywords":"Piping,pipeline","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":650,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}